To reason you do in several school subjects and in many other contexts.
As you reason you develop your thoughts and opinions.
The teacher tells us what you can develop by starting from the knowledge requirements.
The social science states that the pupil should bring nuanced reasoning-
-and describe complex relationships.
So how different things are interconnected.
It can be a little tricky.
How does the students show it?
We change perspectives.
If two ordinary people want to drive the same question-
-What improve school food, is there a difference in who we listen to?
For example, it is about how to say something.
Do you have the habit inside?
Or which words you choose.
The person's socio -economic background plays a role.
It affects how you express itself.
You can be more or less credible.
The background is not decisive whether they were herself affected or witnessed.
But how others interpret what you say also depends on gender and appearance.
The story becomes different depending on the storyteller.
The background can be decisive for who they know.
There are different ways to look at most.
Which perspective have you chosen?
Finally: How are your different arguments related?
Describe the relationship by pointing out similarities and differences.
Then you show more or less complex relationships.
Being able to explain how things are connected, you often benefit.
Both in several school subjects and in other situations outside the school.
Texting: Elisabeth Enström